# MUHAMAD ADI YAKSA

Ciracas, Jakarta Timur, DKI Jakarta Indonesia +6287893319521 muhadiyaksa@gmail.com · linkedin.com/in/muhadiyaksa · github.com/muhadiyaksa

Creative Software Developer and Javascript enthusiast, experienced in using JavaScript from the client and server side such as React JS, Express JS, Node JS and Database Management with MongoDB. Proficient using CSS Frameworks and CSS Preprocessors such as Bootstrap and SASS. Want to learn new things, active, and enjoy meeting with new people.

# **SKILLS**

- Javascript
- Experienced using React JS, Express JS, Node JS.
- Familiar with Redux Concept and Hooks.
- Experienced with CSS framework like a Bootstrap.
- Experienced with CSS Preprocessor like a SASS.
- Able to Program With Object Oriented Programming paradigm.
- Familiar with NoSQL Database like a MongoDB.

- Good Communication
- Problem Solving
- Leadership Ability
- Good Time Management
- Willing to learn something new
- Creative

# **EXPERIENCE**

# **FEBRUARY 2022 – JUNE 2022**

# FRONT END DEVELOPER, PT. HASHMICRO SOLUSI INDONESIA

- 1. Completed the process of designing a responsive static website using HTML, CSS and JAVASCRIPT for HASHMICRO digital marketing purposes.
- 2. Carry out the process of updating the existing content on the website.
- 3. Implementing various animations on the website using a Vanilla Javascript or library such a GSAP.

### **APRIL 2021 – JULY 2022**

# **WEB ADMINISTRATOR, PT. NIAGA BUANA SOLUSI UTAMA**

- 4. Completing the process of preparing products from designing and then uploading them to the ecommerce web
- 5. Performing purchase transaction services in e-commerce web
- 6. Perform the process of improving the appearance on the web using wordpress

# **EDUCATION**

## 2018 - 2022

## UNIVERSITY OF MUHAMMADIYAH PROF. DR. HAMKA

Major In Informatics Engineering Concentrate Multimedia - GPA – 3.66 / 4.0

- Contribute actively as chairman of the media and communication field of the Muhammadiyah Student Association FT UHAMKA for the period 2020-2021.
- Became the Chief Executive of the FMIK 1.0 (Creative Information Media Festival) in 2021 by IMM FT UHAMKA.
- Being a speaker at a routine event of the "Ulik Design" Workshop at IMM FT UHAMKA in 2021.
- Contribute actively as a member of the media and communication field for the Muhammadiyah Student Association of FT UHAMKA for the 2019 2020 period.
- Become a Member of the Publication and Documentation Division of the 2019 Volunteer Initiator Project from BEM UHAMKA.
- Being part of the "IMM FT Teaching" Action at the Nurul Amal Orphanage Foundation, East Jakarta 2019

#### 2015 - 2018

## **SMKN 01 CIKARANG SELATAN**

Major In Computer And Network Engineering

 Contribute actively as a Law Enforcement Officer in the Scout Organization for the 2016-2017 period.

# **PROJECTS**

#### 2022

SAIKA, WEB APP FOR CAMPUS COMMUNITY, FUNDED BY UHAMKA IN PKM 2022 PROGRAM

- Developed using Nodejs, React JS, MongoDB, Express JS, SASS, Bootstrap
- Developed using rest api and rest architecture
- Developed in realtime using socket.io

#### 2022

**PASAR IKAN TAWAR,** WEB MARKETPLACE SPECIFICALLY FOR THE SALE OF FRESHWATER FISH FARMING AS THE COMPLETION OF THE FINAL LECTURE.

## pasarikantawar.herokuapp.com

- Developed using Node JS, React js, Mongodb, Express js, SASS, Bootstrap.
- Developed using rest api and rest . architecture.
- Developed in 2 applications. one for admin and one for user.

## 2021

**TONGKRONGIN,** WEB CREATED TO MAKE IT EASIER TO ORDER PLACES AND FOOD IN CAFES AS THE FINAL PROJECT OF THE COURSE.

## tongkrongin.herokuapp.com

- Developed using Node JS, EJS, Mongodb, Express js, Bootstrap.
- Developed using Monolith architecture.

#### 2021

**MATHCYCLE**, WEBSITE THAT CONTAINS MONTECARLO SIMULATION CALCULATIONS TO PREDICT FUTURE DATA.

# mathcycle.herokuapp.com

- Developed using HTML, CSS and Javascript.
- Statically Developed.